In their town, you don't screw with the law, the law screws with you.
Super Troopers is a comedy, crime, mystery film directed by Jay Chandrasekhar.
Five bored, occasionally high and always ineffective Vermont state troopers
must prove their worth to the governor or lose their jobs.
After stumbling on a drug ring, they plan to make a bust, but a
rival police force is out to steal the glory.
Arcot 'Thorny' Ramathorn, played by Jay Chandrasekhar.
MacIntyre 'Mac' Womack, played by Steve Lemme.
Rodney 'Rod' Farva, played by Kevin Heffernan.
Carl Foster, played by Paul Soter.
John O'Hagen, played by Brian Cox.
Robbie 'Rabbit' Roto, played by Erik Stolhanske.
Super Troopers is a 2001 American comedy film directed by Jay Chandrasekhar and written by and starring the Broken
Lizard comedy group (Chandrasekhar, Kevin Heffernan, Steve Lemme, Paul Soter and Erik Stolhanske).
Marisa Coughlan, Daniel von Bargen and Brian Cox co-star
while Lynda Carter has a cameo appearance.
In total, Fox Searchlight paid $3.25 million for distribution rights of
the film and it grossed $23 million at the box office.
A sequel, Super Troopers 2, was released on April 20, 2018.
The film explores themes of alcohol, police chief, highway, radio, cop.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.